Guide to the American Planning Association records, 1925-2015.
American Planning Association records,
- National APA Conference, "Child Care and the Private Sector", 1987; 749 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Plenary Session with Felix Rohatyn", 1987; 750 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "National Shelter Strategies for Developing Countries", 1987; 751 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Integrating Management and Leadership in City Planning", 1987; 752 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "AICP Review II", 1987 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planning and Building San Antonio", 1988; 802 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Mobilizing the Rural Community", 1988; 803 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "New Jersey's Model Subdivision Ordinance", 1988; 804 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Who's on First? The Politics of Local Government Planning", 1988; 805 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "National Computerized Statistics on Intergovernmental Finance and Economic Development", 1988; 806 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planning and Financing Development Projects After Tax Reform and Deficit Reduction", 1988; 807 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "The Planner/Lawyer Interface", 1988; 808 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Perspectives on Planning Commission Decision Processes", 1988; 809 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Avoiding Regulatory Takings: Recent Cases adn Proof of Damages", 1988; 810 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Promoting Planning Through Public Awareness of American Planning History", 1988; 811 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "From University into Diversity", 1988; 812 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Role for Planners in Devising Revenue Strategies?", 1988; 813 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Architectural Guidelines: Pros and Cons", 1988; 814 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Nonprofit Community Development Organizations in Minority Neighborhoods", 1988; 815 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Yes, in Your Backyard!", 1988; 816 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Opening the City to Persons with Disabilities", 1988; 817 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Avoiding Regulatory Takings: Preventative Measures", 1988; 819 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Case Studies", 1988; 821 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Historical Research and Current Issues in Planning, Public Works, and Policy Making", 1988; 823 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Avoiding Regulatory Takings: Exactions, Dedications, and Impact Fees", 1988; 824 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Women Managers in a Traditionally Male Workplace", 1988; 825 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Meet the Press", 1988; 826 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planning with Blue Ribbon Committees", 1988; 827 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Avoiding Regulatory Takings: Predicting the Future", 1988; 828 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "From Graduate Gowns to Planning Towns", 1988; 829 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Setting Value-Planners and Appraisers", 1988; 830 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Development Impact Fees I", 1988; 832 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planners, Lawmakers, and the Press: Blueprint for Success", 1988; 833 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Pennsylvania Avenue- the President's Walk, the Planners Success Story", 1988; 835 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Performance Zoning Clinic", 1988; 836 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Federal Installations: Who's Doing the Planning?", 1988; 837 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Local-Regional Dispute Resolution: Theory and Practice", 1988; 838 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Public Works: Ensuring America's Future", 1988; 839 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "The Status of Women and Minorities in the Planning Profession", 1988; 840 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Historic Sites and Promotion of Tourism", 1988; 841 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Development Impact Fees II", 1988; 842 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "National Urban Policy", 1988; 843 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Environmental Risk I", 1988; 847 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planning Issues on the Border", 1988; 848 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "San Antonio's Historic Preservation Process", 1988; 849 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Environmental Risk II", 1988; 851 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Metro Denver Network: Computerized Multi-Government Economic Development Information", 1988; 852 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Preserving Subsidized Housing", 1988; 853 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Between Symposium: Modernizing the Statutes: A debate on the Kemp Report", 1992; 230 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Environmental Issues and Minority Communities", 1992; 231 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Fiscal Planning and Tax Rates", 1992; 232 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Bettman Symposium: Modernizing the Statutes: Streamlined Approval for Affordable Housing", 1992; 233 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Reducing Environmental Impacts in Minority Communities", 1992; 234 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Resources and Teaching Kids about Planning", 1992; 235 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Small Town Historic Preservation", 1992; 236 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planning History: Foundations, 1909-1929", 1992; 237 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Environmental Mitigation Impact Fees", 1992; 238 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "APA Journal/ACSP Symposium: Planning Education, Theory, and Practice II", 1992; 239 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Between Symposium: Modernizing the Statutes: Priorities and Cumulative Impacts", 1992; 240 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "AICP/ACSP Symposium: The Future of the Profession", 1992; 241 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Testifying as an Expert Witness", 1992; 242 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Washington Urban Design", 1992; 243 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planners and the Press", 1992; 244 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Wetlands Policy Debate", 1992; 245 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Strategies for Distressed Neighborhoods", 1992; 246 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Tribal Planning and Regional Development", 1992; 247 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planning Commissioners Workshop: Site Plan Review", 1992; 248 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Council of Planning Librarians: Quality of Life in the City", 1992; 249 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Neighborhood Revitalization: Drugs, Crime, and Planners", 1992; 250 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Washington's Living Downtown", 1992; 251 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Urban Design and Preservation in the Nation's Capital", 1992; 252 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Zoning Clinic", 1992; 253 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "How Planners Work: Recent Research", 1992; 254 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "A Practical Discussion of Wetlands", 1992; 255 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Coping with NIMBYs", 1992; 256 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Tax Base Competition in the Baltimore-Washington Corridor", 1992; 257 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Women in Private Practice", 1992; 258 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Council of Planning Librarians: Strategic Planning for Small Communities", 1992; 259 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "AICP Workshop: The Vision Thing: 10 Hot Cases", 1992; 260 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "AICP Workshop: Planning in a Changing Field", 1992; 262 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, Audio Conference Program, "Public Anger and Community Decision-making", 1998 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Intergovernmental and Private Cooperation in Economic Development", 1987; 701 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "International Perspectives in Urban Planning", 1987; 702 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "APA Journal Symposium Impact Fee", 1987; 703 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Billboard Regulation", 1987; 704 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Day Care and Planners", 1987; 705 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Mount Laurel Part I", 1987; 706 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Zoning for Preservation", 1987; 707 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Mount Laurel Part II", 1987; 708 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Sheltering the Homeless", 1987; 709 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Planning for Sexually Oriented Businesses", 1987; 710 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "The Zoning and Subdivision Hearing Examiner", 1987; 711 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Transportation and Economic Development: Evaluation of State and Local Programs", 1987; 712 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "The Law of Impact Fees", 1987; 713 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Creating Central City Home Environments", 1987; 714 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Impact Fees in Florida, Oregon, Colorado, and Canada", 1987; 715 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Supreme Court Cases: The Taking Issues", 1987; 716 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Zoning for Changing Household", 1987; 717 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Impact Fees: Mature and Complex Systems", 1987; 718 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Plenary Sessions", 1987; 719 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Impact Fees: Revamped, and Maturing Systems", 1987; 720 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "The Future of Infrastructure Planning", 1987; 721 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "The Big Three; Planning for Changing CBD Roles and Forms", 1987; 722 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Planning for Conversion form a Military to a Civilian Economy", 1987; 723 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Impact Fees: Economic Issues", 1987; 724 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Impact Fees: Ethical, Social, and Equity Considerations", 1987; 725 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Funeral Installations and Comprehensive Planning", 1987; 726 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Consultant and Counterpart Roles: Project Design Issues", 1987; 727 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Economic Development in Minority Communities", 1987; 728 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Supreme Court Cases: Antitrust, Rent Control, and the Clean Water Act", 1987; 729 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Impact Fees: Linkage Fees for Housing", 1987; 730 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Planning Public Works", 1987; 731 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Developing Better Writing Skills", 1989; 916 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Historic Preservation as a Growth Strategy", 1989; 917 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Case Studies", 1989; 918 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Telecommunications amd Planning", 1989; 920 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Growth Management and State Statutes: the Developer's Case", 1989; 921 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Managing Change Near Federal Installations: Base Closures", 1989; 922 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Comprehensive Planning in Arlington and El Paso", 1989; 923 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Reviving Ctieis with Public Facilities", 1989; 924 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "The Decline of the American Suburb", 1989; 925 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Historic Preservation: An Answer to the Housing Crisis", 1989; 926 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Infrastructure and Impact Fees", 1989; 927 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Planners Planning nad hte Fate of SROs", 1989; 928 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Successful Communities", 1989; 929 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Nineteenth-Century Origins of Planning", 1989; 930 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Growth Management adn Takings Law: Predicting the Future", 1989; 931 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Chapter Delegate Assembly: Send a Message to Lawmakers", 1989; 933 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Development Impact Fees", 1989; 935 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Neighborhood Buyouts 1: Location and the Changing Environment", 1989; 936 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "American City Quality: What is it?", 1989; 937 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Managing Change on Federal Installations: Decisions and Directions", 1989; 938 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "The Ballot Box Revolution in Growth Management", 1989; 939 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Transportation Congestion: what Can We Expect From Existing Solutions?", 1989; 940 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Issues in Private Practice", 1989; 941 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "The Political Agenda Confronting and Challenging Minority Professionals", 1989; 942 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Transit in the Atlanta Region", 1989; 943 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Visions of Planning and Economic Development Cooperation", 1989; 944 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Mitage Environmental Impacts", 1989; 945 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Comprehensive Plans and Zoning Techniques", 1989; 946 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Annexation-Stopping the Pac Man City", 1989; 947 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Neighborhood Buyouts II: Public Policy Consequences", 1989; 948 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Private Practice and Public Agencies: Establishing and Maintaining Linkages", 1989; 949 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Conducting Sucessful Public Meetings", 1989; 950 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Development Impact Fees II", 1989; 952 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Planning for Disaster Relief and Reconstruction", 1989; 953 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Performance Planning: Using Indicators to Change the Terms of Public Discourse", 1989; 954 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "The Greenhouse Effect: When Does the Planning Start?", 1989; 955 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Geographic Information Systems in Dynamic Planning Environments", 1989; 957 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Performance Zoning Clinic", 1989; 958 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "State and Local Planning", 1989; 959 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Conflict between Planning Managers and Professional Employees: Is it Inevitable?", 1989; 960 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "new Wave Technologies: Putting the Gee-Whiz to Work", 1989; 961 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Trash and Cash: Solid Waste as a Revenue Generator", 1989; 963 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "New Developments in Development", 1989; 964 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Low-Income Housing Finance: The Local Role", 1989; 965 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Lobbying Skills for Planners", 1989; 966 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "The Fair Housing Act", 1989; 967 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Planning for Tenant Management Activities", 1989; 968 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Planning for Infrastructure Support of Economic Development", 1989; 969 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Specific Plans for Districts", 1989; 970 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Environmental Protection and Urban Development in teh Caribeean Basin", 1989; 971 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Breaking the Glass Ceiling: Skills for Women Advancing in teh Planning Profession I", 1989; 972 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Breaking the Glass Ceiling: Skills for Women Advancing in the Planning Profession II", 1989; 973 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Role of Nongovernmental Organizations in Self-Help Housing Programs", 1989; 974 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "The Effectiveness of Cluster Development", 1989; 975 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Responding to the Takings Issue", 1989; 976 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Tourism Planning", 1989; 977 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Energy Management Programs: The Utility Interface", 1989; 978 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Plenary Luncheon (Whyte)", 1989; 979 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Strategic Management for the Public and Nonprofit Sectors", 1989; 980 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Project Management", 1989; 981 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Atlanta's Central Area Study", 1989; 982 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Measuring Unnecessary Hardship for Variances", 1989; 983 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Granny Flats Forum", 1989; 983 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "???", 1989; 984 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Places as Art: Design of the Public Realm", 1989; 985 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Conjuring Visions/Mastering Change", 1989; 986 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Principles of Site Plan Review", 1989; 987 (Box 88)
- National APA Conference, "Program Evaluation for Agencies", 2000; 081 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Innovative Regional Growth Management", 2000; 082 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Reuses for Ellis Island", 2000; 083 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Making Great Places", 2000; 084 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Urban Resources Partnership", 2000; 085 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "AICP Exam Prep, Part II", 2000; 086 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Getting the Performance You Want", 2000; 087 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Advanced Negotiation Skills for Planners", 2000; 088 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "The Mission Corridor", 2000; 089 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "AICPJ/ACSP Collaborative Projects Symposium", 2000; 090 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "A New Generation of TDRs", 2000; 091 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Women Planners as Leaders", 2000; 092 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Community-Sensitive Transportation Projects", 2000; 093 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "A New Look at Urban Renewal", 2000; 094 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Civic Technologies", 2000; 095 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Small Town Planning Office", 2000; 096 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Green Mapping", 2000; 097 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, " Evolving Role of Bids", 2000; 098 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Challenge-Proof Sign Ordinances", 2000; 099 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Computers and the 21st Century", 2000; 0100 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Humanizing Streets", 2000; 0101 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Corridors and Community Development", 2000; 0102 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Myths and Facts on Community Development", 2000; 0104 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Neighorhoods of Choice", 2000; 0105 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Central City Industrial Land", 2000; 0106 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Neighorhood Commercial Revitalization", 2000; 0108 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Aesthetis, Community Character and the Law", 2000; 0109 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Parks and Urban Revitalization", 2000; 0110 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Next Generation American Cities", 2000; 0111 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Planning and Zoning as Strange Bedfellows", 2000; 0112 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Talking Ethics", 2000; 0113 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Visual Interactive Code", 2000; 0115 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Preserving Community Character", 2000; 0116 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Whose Vision Will Control Tribal Gaming?", 2000; 0117 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Multi-Jurisdictional Cooperatino in Long-Range Transportation Planning", 2000; 0118 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Zoning Out Gay Businesses", 2000; 0119 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "University-Sponsored Neighborhood Revitalization", 2000; 0120 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "New York City's New Waterfront", 2000; 0121 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Planning Game Show", 2000; 0122 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Non-Planners and Growth Management", 2000; 0123 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Protecting New York City's Watersheds", 2000; 0124 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Progressive Regional Planning", 2000; 0125 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Census 2000", 0126 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Partnering With Federal Agencies", 2000; 0127 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Helping Planners Publish", 2000; 0128 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Sustainable Rural Economic Redevelopment", 2000; 0129 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Grade Your Planning Department", 2000; 0130 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Masering Priorities", 2000; 0131 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Faith-Based CSCS as Partners", 2000; 0132 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Essential Skills for Planners in Spacial Analysis", 2000; 0133 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "American Heritage Rivers", 2000; 0134 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Are Subsidies Worth It?", 2000; 0135 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Lessons for the Forefront in Housing", 2000; 0136 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Israel Stollman's Ethical Planning", 2000; 0137 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Progressive Planning and Environmental Justice", 2000; 0138 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Staet Programs taht Bust Sprawl", 2000; 0139 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "A New Visioning Process for Growing Smart", 2000; 0140 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Technology for Citizen Decision Making", 2000; 0141 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "The New Jersey State Plan", 2000; 0142 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Running Smart Meetings", 2000; 0143 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Urban Manufacturing", 2000; 0144 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Health Centers and Community Development", 2000; 0145 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Credentialing, Licensing or Nothing", 2000; 0146 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Small Towns and Counties Growing Smarter", 2000; 0147 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Telecommunications Impact on Urban Development", 2000; 0148 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Putting the Public in Planning", 2000; 0149 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Sustainable Inner Ring Suburbs", 2000; 0150 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Tea-21 Overview", 2000; 0151 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Increasing Street Connectivity", 2000; 0152 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Green Infrastructure", 2000; 0153 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Bus Rapid Transit", 2000; 0154 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Mount Laurel", 2000; 0155 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Creating Town Centers", 2000; 0156 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "How to Acquire Parklands in a Major City", 2000; 0157 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Living in New Towns", 2000; 0158 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Closing General Session: A Pioneer and His Legacy", 2000; 0159 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Strengthening Local Government Capacity", 2000; 0160 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Urban Parks and Decision Makers", 2000; 0161 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Regulating Monster Homes", 2000; 0163 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Suburban Wildlife Preservation", 2000; 0164 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Strengthening Communities through Tourism", 2000; 0165 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Harnessing Workflow to the Web", 2000; 0166 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "New Models for Infrastructure Planning", 2000; 0167 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Using Positive Influence: Communicating to get what you want", 2000; 0168 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Approaches to Land-use and Land Characteristics Analysis", 2000; 0169 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Safescape", 2000; 0170 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Work Agreements and Contracts", 2000; 0171 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Successful Planning Statute Reform", 2000; 0172 (Box 89)
- National APA Conference, "Demystifying Public Finance", 2000; 0173 (Box 89)